Guide to the Wrexham Foundation, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Wrexham Foundation, Yale University, records
1950-1998
RU 915
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
23.75
The records consist of correspondence, member lists, minutes, and ledgers documenting the activities and operations of the Manuscript Society (incorporated as the Wrexham Foundation).
Wrexham Foundation, Inc
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Wrexham Foundation, 2002.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. Requests for access must be directed to Stephen Parks, or his successor, for approval.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, member lists, minutes, and ledgers documenting the activities and operations of the Manuscript Society (incorporated as the Wrexham Foundation).
College students -- Societies, etc.; Secret societies -- United States; Wrexham Foundation, Inc; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students
- Records of the Manuscript Society, 1952-1997; Accession 2003-A-031
  - House files
    - 1952-1964 (Box 1)
    - 1965 (Box 2)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - 1975-1984 (Box 4)
    - 1985-1987 (Box 5)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 7)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 9)
    - 1996 (Box 10)
    - 1997 (Box 11)
  - Member lists, circa 1950-1984 (Box 12)
  - Minutes, handbooks(oversize), 1953-1968 (Box 13)
  - David Calleo files
    - General files, 1969-2001 (Box 14–15)
    - Investments, circa 1982-1996 (Box 16)
- Trustees minutes, 1955-1972; Accession 2007-A-025